solex.com 2011-09-08

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

## Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. We understand that you entrust us with your private financial information to help the Dealer match you with a bank or lender (we refer to all of these as "Lenders") who can meet your needs. Rest assured that we protect your privacy. Under no circumstances will Solex sell or share any personal information about you to or with any person or organization except: as authorized by you to participating Lenders, or other parties involved in your transaction, or as may be required by law or court order. The Privacy Policy below describes the standards we adhere to in handling information about you and your loan request.

### Who We Are

Solex develops, owns and maintains private sites that are only accessed by recreation or leisure-marina Dealers (collectively “Dealers”) that have been approved and have entered into a written agreement with us. Dealers use these systems to enter personal information about their customers. Based on the information you supply to the Dealer, Solex will transmit your data to participating Lenders who are best suited to meet your financial needs. Only Lenders who the Dealer has a pre-existing agreement with can receive your information. Any personal information that is entered by the Dealer can be submitted to one or more participating Lenders.

Solex does not collect any personal information about you unless you choose to provide that information to the Dealer. If you are providing personal information to a Dealer that is using Solex, the Dealer may be required to have you agree online (by a click on an “I accept” button) and sign a form of consent to such action. This is your permission for the Dealer to transmit your personal information to the Lenders.

### Privacy Policy 

Our primary goal is to aid Dealers in the collection of your personal information and then transmit this information to a Lender(s) in a highly efficient and secure manner in order to secure financing for the asset purchase you are completing with the Dealer. As part of the normal operation of that service, we collect and send your personal information to the Lender(s) directed by the Dealer.

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. Any personal information that can identify you is deleted from our database as determined by federal privacy law.

Except as otherwise expressly discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are Dealers or Lenders on our system or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use of the personal information you disclose to them. Since Solex does not control the privacy policies of third parties, including Dealers, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### Opt Out Alternatives

Solex provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of sending your personal information to any Lender utilizing Solex services. Please ask your Dealer for a list of their approved Lenders.

### Our Commitment To Data Security  

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall, encryption and password protection systems to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, there is no such thing as perfect security on the Internet. 

We may use a small text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of our Dealer’s computer to guide our users through our applications. The cookie itself does not contain any Personal Information, although it will enable us to relate the use of this site by the Dealer to the information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. Cookies are harmless to your Dealer’s computer.

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 866-483-4175 or send us an email at [info@solex.com](mailto:info@solex.com)
